http://lighthousefm.org/privacy/

Donate Now
Choose:
Pre-Authorized Debit Agreement Form
Underwriting
Get the app!
Listen Live!
Privacy
What information do we collect? How do we use it?
When you donate or enter a contest or other promotional feature, we may ask for your name, address, and e-mail address or other information. This is so that we can administer the donation or contest, and notify winners or contact donors.
How does Lighthouse FM protect my information if I make an online donation with my credit card?
We use a Secure Server for collecting personal and credit card information. The secure sockets layer (SSL) encrypts (scrambles) all of the information you enter before it is transmitted over the internet and sent to us. Furthermore, all of the data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. Our secure server services are administered by our web host, GoDaddy. When you log into the secure section of our site, you will see GoDaddy’s identity in the page’s security settings. This is completely normal.
What about “cookies”?
“Cookies” are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, but they do enable us to provide download capabilities for software and other files.
Will Lighthouse FM disclose the information it collects to outside parties?
Lighthouse FM does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. We may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third-party vendors, but these statistics will not include personally identifying information. Lighthouse FM may release account information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) comply with law, (ii) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements or (iii) protect the rights, property or safety of Lighthouse FM, our users, or others.
Summary
In summary, Lighthouse FM is committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to enhance your overall online experience. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others.
Consent
By using the Lighthouse FM web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Lighthouse FM. Changes to our privacy policy we will posted on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. Lighthouse FM also provides links to affiliated sites. The privacy policies of these linked sites are the responsibility of the linked site and Lighthouse FM has no control or influence over their policies. Please check the policies of each site you visit for specific information. Lighthouse FM cannot be held liable for damage or misdoings of other sites linked or otherwise.
